https://fuelsafe.com/policies

Motorsports
Fuel CellsUniversalPro Cell®Sportsman®Spectra-LiteEnduro®Core®Race Safe®Aluminum Fuel CellsOff-RoadOval TrackDirt Late ModelNASCARSprint CarFormula TransAmDrag RacingModel SpecificFuel Cell PartsFuel Delivery SystemsFuel PumpsRegulatorsWiring HarnessesCollectors / Surge TanksFiltersFittingsPick Up AccessoriesSending Units / GaugesFuel Filler AccessoriesDry BreaksDisplacement BlocksDump CansFender AdaptersFuel CapsFill / Vent HoseFuel Safe Outlet
Marine / Subsea
Military Defense
Aviation
Industrial
Secondary Containment
Custom / Capabilities
Menu
Motorsports
PRIVACY POLICIES
Aircraft Rubber Manufacturing, Inc. dba Fuel Safe Systems is concerned about privacy matters for its customers, and is committed to protecting our customer’s privacy and personal information.
By accessing this web site, you agree to the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. We reserve the right to make revisions to this policy and our other terms and conditions at any time, and will post those policies on our web site.
Our websites contain links to dealers and other third parties which are not under our control. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of any such linked site.
INFORMATION: Customers are welcome to view our websites at any time without providing any personal information. When making a purchase of our product, we need to obtain certain information about you including your name, e-mail and mailing addresses, and your billing information so we can fill, confirm and ship the order, or contact you about the status of your order.
PERSONAL DATA: We will not use, disclose, sell, trade or disseminate any credit card holder data entered on the shopping cart payment form to any third parties except as necessary to process cardholder orders, process refunds, resolve Chargebacks, or as required by subpoena or order by a court or other governmental agency. Your shipping address and telephone number will be provided to a third party for delivery of your order.
Processing orders through our online certified shopping cart requires you to enter credit card information. Our shopping cart integrates with Authorize.Net® and the credit card processors using the highest payment gateway security standards. In addition, we have subscribed to their credit card security features. We will use all reasonable efforts to safeguard the confidentiality of your information; however, we will not be responsible for disclosure of any information due to errors in transmission or the unauthorized acts of third parties.
NON-PERSONAL DATA: For administration purposes, this site may use cookies and/or collect your IP address or domain name. No personal information is obtained in this manner. If you choose not to take advantage of cookies, you may set your browser to refuse them.
RETURN POLICIES
The following rules apply to product returns. For information regarding our product warranty, please see the Limited Warranty statement.
All returns require a Return Merchandise Authorization (RMA) number, pre-approval, and must be accompanied by a copy of the original invoice. To obtain an RMA number, call 800-433-6524 or by e-mail to sales@fuelsafe.com.
Returns are subject to a minimum value of $75.
All returns are subject to a minimum 20% or minimum $35 restocking fee (unless you were shipped the wrong product).
Returns must be new and in saleable condition. Care must be taken to pack the item to avoid scratches, surface wear or other damage in shipment. Fuel Safe is not responsible for freight damage on return shipments. Please insure the items appropriately.
Label the RMA number on the outside of the shipping box.
All items must be returned to us freight prepaid by customer; any items shipped COD will be refused.
All items must be in the current price list or shopping cart item list and purchased within the last 30 days.
No exchanges or returns of any custom product or any standard product that has been modified at your request; e.g. cut hose, modified plates, etc.
If a used cell is shipped to Fuel Safe for any reason, it must be clean and dry or it will be subject to a hazardous material disposal fee.
Electronic items are not returnable.
Credit for returned product may be used towards the purchase of replacement product only, must be used within 12 months, and cannot be refunded in cash.
If you receive an order that was damaged in shipment, retain all boxes and packing materials and contact us for further instructions @ 800-433-6524.
Returns should be sent to Fuel Safe Systems, 1550 NE Kingwood Ave., Redmond OR 97756.
SECURITY POLICIES
The security of your information is very important to us. To protect that information, we maintain reasonable physical, procedural and technical measures to limit access to authorized individuals.
We utilize a certified shopping cart on our website, which sends transactions to the payment gateway using an end-to-end Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) connection to encrypt and transmit your credit card information. SSL is one of the highest levels of transaction security protocols available. This payment process connects through Authorize.Net® which adds another layer of fraud detection tools to protect against misuse of credit cards.
Even though we take these measures to protect and secure your personal data, we cannot guarantee that all electronic commerce is completely secure.
If you believe that someone has improperly used personally identifiable information about you or has made purchases that you did not authorize, please contact us or your credit card company immediately.
